Cole, David L. Papers 5588
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Maritime Transport Lines, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  3/13/75. Issue: rates of pay; premium pay; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Permanente Steamship Corporation, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 1-2)
  Issue: rates of pay; transcript; correspondence; exhibit; hearing notes
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Trinidad Corporation, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  12/24/73. Issue: discharge; alcoholism; hearing notes; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Moore-McCormack Lines, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  10/26/73. Issue: discharge; insubordination; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Moore-McCormack Lines, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  10/12/72. Issue: rates of pay; severance pay; hearing notes; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Prudential Grace Lines, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  9/26/72. Issue: rates of pay; back pay; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Permanente Steamship Company, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 2)
  Correspondence (no award)
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Prudential Grace Lines, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  4/19/72. Issue: discharge; insubordination; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Lykes Brothers Steamship Company, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 4)
  3/17/72. Issue: discharge; unsatisfactory job performance; hearing notes; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Keystone Shipping Company, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  5/27/71. Issue: discharge; hearing notes; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. United States Lines, 1971 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  5/27/71. Issue: reinstatement; illness; hearing notes; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. SS Valley Forge/SS Carbide Seadrift, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  12/29/70. Issue: overtime; unsatisfactory job performance; hearing notes; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Gulf and South American Steamship Company, 1970 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  3/16/70. Issue: illegal work stoppage; hearing notes; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Lykes Brothers Steamship Company, 1969 (Box 118, Folder 9)
  4/22/69. Issue: rates of pay "Vietnam Area Bonus;" correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Lykes Brothers Steamship Company, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 10)
  12/17/68. Issue: discharge; job performance; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Grace Lines, 1968 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  5/1/68. Issue: discharge; fights and altercation; correspondence; exhibit
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association (Box 118, Folder 12)
  8/16/67. Issue: rates of pay; hearing notes; exhibit; correspondence
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. MSC, 1965-1970 (Box 118, Folder 13-15)
  Correspondence regarding various issues
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1966-1969 (Box 118, Folder 16-19)
  Correspondence regarding meetings of Licensed Personnel Board and other related matters
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Pacific Maritime Association, 1967-1977 (Box 119, Folder 1-3)
  Correspondence regarding Licensed Personnel Board
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Pacific Maritime Association, 1967 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  11/21/67. Issue: renegotiation of agreement; grievance procedure
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Pacific Maritime Association, 1967-1969 (Box 119, Folder 5-7)
  Hearing notes; summary of case
- Marine Engineers Beneficial Association vs. Pacific Maritime Association, 1966 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  Exhibit; data regarding wages and costs of settlement in above case
- Metropolitan Opera Association, Incorporated vs. American Federation of Musicians, 1961-1966 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  Includes correspondence; Arthur J. Goldberg decision
- Metropolitan Opera Association, Incorporated vs. American Federation of Musicians, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  Includes correspondence; hearing notes
- Milk Dealers' Labor Committee of Greater New York and New Jersey vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1948-1962 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  10/23/48 - 1/15/62. Hearing notes only.
- Milk Dealers' Association of Metropolitan New York vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1947 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  12/15/47. Includes correspondence; hearing notes
- Milk Industry - Drivers and Dairy Employees Unions, Pension and Welfare Fund vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 338, 584, 602, 607 and 680, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  11/30/51. Issue: mandatory retirement age under the pension and welfare fund; includes correspondence, briefs, hearing notes
- Milk Industry - Milk Dealers of New Jersey, Borden's Farm Products of New Jersey, Clinton Milk Company, Consumers Dairy Company, Hamilton Farms Incorporated, and others vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 68, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  2/3/54. Issue: holiday pay; includes correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit
- Milk and Cream Company, Newark vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 680, 1954 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  2/13/54. Issue: discharge
- Milk Dealers' Labor Committee of Greater New York and Northern New Jersey vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Locals 338, 584, 602, 607 and 680, 1948 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  10/25/48. Issue: rates of pay; includes stipulation to arbitrate, correspondence, exhibit
- Milk Dealers, New York and New Jersey vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 584, units 1, 2, and 3, and Locals 680 and 338, 1945 (Box 124, Folder 2-3)
  5/31/45. Issue: job classification; shift premium; work week; includes correspondence, exhibit, reports, briefs, hearing notes
- Milk Dealers: New York & New Jersey, Text (Box 124.1, Folder 1)
- Mohawk Airlines, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1970-1971 (Box 125, Folder 1-5)
  Issues: seniority, vacations, recall following strike; includes reports, correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit and 3/31/71 decision
- Mohawk Airlines, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1970-1971 (Box 126, Folder 1-4)
  Issues: rates of pay, hours of work; includes reports, correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit and 5/10/71 decision
- National Airlines, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 127, Folder 1-2)
  6/17/57. Issue: pension plan; includes correspondence, exhibit
- National Labor Relations Board vs. Pacific American Ship-owners Association and others, 1952 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  Includes correspondence, consent decree
- National League of Professional Baseball Clubs and American League of Professional Baseball Clubs vs. Major League Baseball Players Association, 1970 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  6/17/70. Issue: World Series Fund division among teams
- National Screen Service Corporation vs. Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild, 1948 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  Includes transcripts in a case regarding rates of pay
- Neumann, R. and Company vs. International Fur and Leather Workers Union, 1949 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  Hearing notes regarding work stoppage, employee discharge
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, 1948 (Box 129, Folder 3-4)
  Hearing notes, correspondence, exhibit regarding union shop, rates of pay
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. Telephone Workers Union of New Jersey, 1948 (Box 130, Folder 1)
  8/48. Includes exhibits and notes of company position in above case
- New Jersey Bell Telephone Company vs. Communication Workers of America, 1948 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  Includes report by New Jersey State Board of Mediation appointed hearing panel (Cole was a member)
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1947 (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
  2/19/47. Issues: vacations, incentive pay, rates of pay; includes hearing notes, correspondence, briefs
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1950 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  12/50. Hearing notes regarding rates of pay
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1947-1948 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  Hearing notes and agreement regarding bonus pay, lunch period and sanitary code
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1947 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  Grievance forms (completed) regarding seniority, rates of pay, etc.
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1949 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  7/13/49. Issue: incentive pay
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1949 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  5/31/49. Issue: seniority
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1951 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  8/20/51. Issue: piece rate
- New Jersey Worsted Mills (NJWM) vs. Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA), 1951 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  11/20/51. Issues: rates of pay, holiday pay, hours of work
- New York Central Railroad Company vs. Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1956 (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
  6/4/56. Issue: work week; includes correspondence, exhibit
- New York (City of) vs. Sergeants Benevolent Association and Lieutenants Benevolent Association and Uniformed Fire Officers Association, Local 854, International Association of Fire Fighters, 1968 (Box 133, Folder All)
  1/24/68. Issues: rates of pay, salary schedules; includes transcripts, correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit, briefs, reports
- New York (City of) vs. Sergeants Benevolent Association and Lieutenants Benevolent Association and Uniformed Fire Officers Association, Local 854, International Association of Fire Fighters, 1968 (Box 134, Folder All)
- New York (City of) vs. Sergeants Benevolent Association and Lieutenants Benevolent Association and Uniformed Fire Officers Association, Local 854, International Association of Fire Fighters, 1968 (Box 135, Folder All)
- New York (City of) vs. Sergeants Benevolent Association and Lieutenants Benevolent Association and Uniformed Fire Officers Association, Local 854, International Association of Fire Fighters, 1968 (Box 136, Folder All)
- New York (City of) vs. Sergeants Benevolent Association and Lieutenants Benevolent Association and Uniformed Fire Officers Association, Local 854, International Association of Fire Fighters, 1968 (Box 137, Folder All)
- New York (City of) Board of Education vs. United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1965 (Box 138, Folder 1-2)
  Includes hearing notes, report, correspondence, exhibit
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 139, Folder All)
  6/18/47. Issues: rates of pay, terms of contract, pension plan; includes hearing notes, correspondence, exhibit, minutes of arbitration hearings 3-4/47, briefs, reports, transcripts
- Minutes of Arbitration Hearings - New York City Omnibus Corporation vs Transport Workers Union: March - April 1947 -- [bound volume], Text (Box 139.1, Folder 1)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 140, Folder All)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 141, Folder All)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 142, Folder All)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 143, Folder All)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation: Transport Workers Union of America - Testimony in Arbitration proceedings Before David L. Cole -- Vol. 1 - Pages 1 to 666, Text (Box 143, Folder 1)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 144, Folder All)
- New York City Omnibus Corporation; Madison Avenue Coach Company, Incorporated; Eighth Avenue Coach Corporation vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 144.1, Folder 1)
  Additional exhibits
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1951 (Box 144.1, Folder 2)
  Exhibits describing the Board of Transportation
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 144.1, Folder 3)
  12/61. Exhibits and report, recommendations of the Transit Labor Board; issues: four day work week, health program, rates of pay
- New York City Transit Authority vs. All Interested Employee Labor Organizations, 1957 (Box 145, Folder All)
  Hearing notes, exhibits, transcripts, briefs, reports, statements, proceedings to determine appropriate units (Fact-finding Committee for New York City)
- New York City Transit Authority vs. All Interested Employee Labor Organizations, 1957 (Box 145.1, Folder All)
- New York City Transit Authority vs. All Interested Employee Labor Organizations, 1957 (Box 145.2, Folder All)
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1948-1950 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  Exhibits, reports from the Board of Transportation and the New York City Transit Fact-finding Board
- New York City Transit Authority vs. Transport Workers Union of America, 1950 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  3/50. Exhibit presented to Fact-finding Board in the Transit Industry from the Board of Transportation and the Union
- New York Herald Tribune vs. Newspaper Guild, 1960 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  3-8/60. Hearing notes discussing sick pay, vacation pay
- New York Telephone vs. United Telephone Organization, 1948 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  Hearing notes discussing sick benefits, insurance plan
- New York Typographical Union Number Six vs. Publishers Association of New York City, 1953 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  Correspondence, agreement
- New York World Telegram vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1947 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  2/17/47. Issue: wage re-opener
- New York World Telegram vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1949 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  Exhibits, briefs presented to voluntary Labor Arbitration Tribunal regarding rates of pay
- New York World Telegram and Sun vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1950 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  12/20/50. Issue: vacation pay
- New York World Telegram and Sun vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1951 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  5/14/51. Issue: shift differentials, rates of pay
- News Syndicate Company vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1947 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  10-11/47. Statements and rebuttals by both parties prior to arbitration; issue: minimum wage rates and shift differentials
- Newspaper Publishers Association of Philadelphia vs. Philadelphia Newspaper Printing Pressman's Union, 1949 (Box 149, Folder 2-3)
  3-4/49. Articles, exhibits regarding rates of pay
- Newspaper Publishers Association of Philadelphia vs. Philadelphia Newspaper Printing Pressman's Union, 1949 (Box 150, Folder 1-2)
  Additional transcripts, exhibits
- Newsweek vs. Newspaper Guild of New York, 1948 (Box 151, Folder 1-3)
  7/24/48. Issue: discharge, reinstatement; includes transcript, brief, correspondence, exhibit
- Newsweek (Hearst Publishers) vs. New York Newspaper Guild, 1950 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  1/27/50. Transcript of proceeding before Cole regarding wage opener
- North American Aviation, Incorporated vs. United Auto Workers, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  8/15/52. Hearing notes regarding wage demands
- North American Aviation, Incorporated vs. United Auto Workers, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  9/13/52. Issue: rates of pay; includes correspondence, briefs, hearing notes, exhibits
- Northwest Airline Pilots, American Airline Pilots vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1951-1952 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  Contracts only
- Oakes Woolen Company vs. unidentified union, 1946 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  9/17/46. Hearing notes regarding discharge
- Oppenheimer - Collins vs. United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  2/2/47. Hearing notes regarding wage adjustment
- Pan American Airways, Incorporated vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  9/24/47. Issue: layoff, seniority; includes correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit
- Pan American Airways, Incorporated vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1947 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  12/16/47. Issue: rates of pay, job classification; includes correspondence, hearing notes, transcript
- Pan American Airways, Incorporated vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1948 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  11/10/48. Issue: rates of pay, severance pay; includes correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit
- Pan American Airways, Incorporated vs. Transport Workers Union of America, Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1948 (Box 154, Folder 1)
- Pan American Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, International, 1952 (Box 155, Folder 1-2)
  5/1/52. Issue: seniority; includes exhibit
- Pan American Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, International, 1952 (Box 156, Folder 1-4)
  Includes transcripts, correspondence, hearing notes and exhibits in above case and supplemental hearing, - 5-7/52.
- Pan American World Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  1/57. Issue: jurisdiction; includes hearing notes, correspondence, briefs
- Pan American World Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1956 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  4/11/56. Issue: rates of pay, grievance procedure
- Pan American World Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 157, Folder 1-3)
  6/57. Issues: rates of pay, work rules, working conditions; includes correspondence, exhibit, reports, hearing notes
- Pan American World Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1957 (Box 158, Folder 1-2)
  Exhibits and final report of neutral (Cole)
- Pan American World Airways, Incorporated vs. Airline Pilots Association, 1962 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  5/24/62. Issues: vacations, sick leave, pay adjustment, retirement; includes exhibit, correspondence, hearing notes
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company and Baltimore and Eastern Railroad Company vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1950 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  5/5/50. Includes exhibits, correspondence
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company vs. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1951 (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
  12/12/51. Issue: telephone usage; includes correspondence, hearing notes, exhibit
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company vs. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Order of Railroad Telegraphers, 1951 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  Exhibits
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, Long Island Railroad Company, Baltimore and Eastern Railroad Company vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, 1950 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  3/27/50. Includes briefs, exhibits
- Philadelphia National League Baseball Club vs. Major League Baseball Players Association, 1969 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  8/25/69. Issue: discharge; includes exhibit, correspondence, hearing notes, transcript
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1950 (Box 163, Folder 1-5)
  10/11/50. Issues: rates of pay, overtime, pension plan, funeral pay, vacation pay; includes correspondence, briefs, hearing notes, exhibit, transcript
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1950 (Box 164, Folder 1)
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. Utility Company Workers' Association, 1950 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  11/50. Includes hearing notes, contract, correspondence
- Public Service Electric and Gas Company vs. Utility Company Workers' Association, 1951 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  3/8/51. Issue: job elimination; includes correspondence
- Publishers' Association of New York City vs. New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union Number Two, 1954 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  8/3/54. Issues: wage changes, wage formulas
- Publishers' Association of New York City vs. New York Newspaper Printing Pressmen's Union Number Two, 1955 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  12/28/55. Issue: crew size; includes exhibit, correspondence, hearing notes
- Quality Transportation vs. International Longshoremen's Association, United Marine Division, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  8/9/49. Hearing notes only
- Railroad Industry vs. Rail Unions, 1951 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  12/11/51. Hearing notes only
- Railroad Industry - non-operators vs. Rail Unions, 1948 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  10/26/48. Hearing notes only
- Railway Express Agency vs. not given, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  4/17/49. Hearing notes only
- Reinauer Transportation vs. International Longshoremen's Association, United Marine Division, Local 333, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  11/28/49. Issue: retroactive wage increase, overtime allowances, job related modifications; includes correspondence, exhibit
- Republic Aviation vs. International Association of Machinists, 1960 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  6/1/60. Hearing notes only
- Republic Pictures Corporation vs. Screen Office and Professional Employees Guild, Local 109, 1948 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  1/26/48. Hearing notes, transcripts
- Rochelle Park Velvet Company vs. not given, 1952 (Box 165, Folder 9)
  9/22/52. Hearing notes only
- Ronson Art Metal Works, Incorporated vs. United Auto Workers, Local 589, 1953 (Box 165, Folder 10)
  Includes correspondence
- Ronson Stock Purchases, 1960 (Box 166, Folder 1)
- Ronson Corporation, 1967-1971 (Box 166, Folder 2-7)
  Includes correspondence, bills, reports, orders, newspaper articles, petition for exemption from equal employment opportunity (EEO) rules
- Ronson Corporation, 1965-1967 (Box 167, Folder 1-4)
  Includes correspondence, reports regarding Ronson vs. Braun Company
- Ronson Corporation vs. Braun Company arbitration, 1967 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  6/30/67. Report of proceedings in the Court of Arbitration of the International Chamber of Commerce; includes correspondence
- Ronson Corporation, 1955-1977 (Box 169, Folder 1-4)
  Correspondence; contracts; correspondence regarding excise tax on cigarette lighters, regarding 1955 contract negotiations with the United Auto Workers in Newark plant and routine
- Rose Hosiery Company vs. American Federation of Hosiery Workers, 1942 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  12/14/42. Issue: differential wage rates
- Schenck Transportation Company vs. Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1949 (Box 170, Folder 1-2)
  Hearing notes, exhibits
- Schenley Industries, Incorporated vs. Brewery Workers, 1953 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  1953. Correspondence
- Screen Actors Guild vs. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1959 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  Hearing notes regarding merger
- Silver Rod Stores, Incorporated vs. United Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Employees, Congress of Industrial Organizations, Local 146, 1942 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  12/31/42. Issue: discharge, probationary period; hearing notes